The Daniel Craig story.
Being James Bond is a documentary film directed by Baillie Walsh.
Daniel Craig candidly reflects on his 15 year adventure as James Bond.
Including never-before-seen archival footage from Casino Royale to the upcoming 25th film No Time To Die, Craig
shares his personal memories in conversation with 007 producers, Michael G Wilson and Barbara Broccoli.
Self (voice), played by Daniel Craig.
Self - Producer (voice), played by Michael G. Wilson.
Self - Producer (voice), played by Barbara Broccoli.
Self (archive footage), played by Harrison Ford.
Self (archive footage), played by Rami Malek.
James Bond is a fictional character and the titular protagonist of Eon Productions'
rebooted James Bond film series, first introduced in the 2006 film Casino Royale.
Portrayed by British actor Daniel Craig, this interpretation of the character, and the actor portraying him, received critical praise for a "caustic,
haunted, intense reinvention of 007" – a darker, more realistic tone than the lighter characterisations portrayed in past Bond films.
The rebooted series spanned five films—Casino Royale (2006), Quantum of Solace (2008),
Skyfall (2012), Spectre (2015), and No Time to Die (2021)—all starring Craig.
This version of Bond is killed at the end of the lattermost film, making him, to date, the
only version of the character in the Eon Productions James Bond films to die.